<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyTourGuide</string>
    <string name="popular_cities">Popular Cities</string>
    <string name="kerala">Kerala</string>
    <string name="zurich">Zurich</string>
    <string name="paris">Paris</string>
    <string name="dublin">Dublin</string>
    <string name="popular_tours">Popular Tours</string>
    <string name="placeholder_tourcost">Euro 50 per person</string>
    <string name="placeholder_tourTime">10 hours</string>

    <string name="dubtogal">Travel with us on one of our wonderful day trips from Dublin to the Cliffs of Moher in
        County Clare. Located on Ireland\’s wild rugged Atlantic coast, the cliffs were recently voted as the seventh
        most wonderful heritage site in the world in a global poll conducted by UNESCO. Enjoy the breath-taking scenery
        of Ireland\’s rugged West Coast as we travel along the spectacular Wild Atlantic Way to one of Ireland\’s national
        treasures and a UNESCO Global Geopark, the Burren. Visit the medieval city of Galway and enjoy a 30-minute guided
        tour of this historic and vibrant city, widely known as Ireland\’s most Irish city, before returning
        to Dublin with wonderful memories.</string>
    <string name="dubtobel">Giant\’s Causeway and Belfast city day tour passing through the Boyne Valley, home to the
        five thousand year old Hill of Tara, the ancient capital of the High Kings of Ireland. Learn about the Battle
        of Boyne between King James (Catholic) and King William of Orange (Protestant – Dutch), a chapter in history
        which was hugely significant in the political, cultural and religious destinies of both Ireland and Britain.
        Crossing the border into the north of Ireland, your guide will have some fascinating observations for you to see.
        On your Belfast tour you will immediately observe how different it will look compared to Dublin.
        Belfast was the only city in Ireland which experienced the Industrial Revolution of Britain during the 19th
        century</string>
    <string name="parischarms">From the majestic Louvre to the regal Palais Royal,this neighbourhood oozes luxury.
        The grand arches along Rue de Rivoli are shadowed by mosaics in front of decorated vitrines and hotels.
        Place Vendôme is lined with the world\’s best jewelers and their glittering window displays.
        Every other establishment has someone to open the door for you or park your car.You can spend hours gazing
        at its haute couture shops or lingering over a meal at any of its chic eateries.After all that indulgence,
        the Tuileries gardens provide stately respite, while theatres compete for your applause.
        It is a neighbourhood that draws admirers from around the world, all attracted to the luxe life in Paris.</string>
    <string name="parisfood">Embark on a culinary tour of Paris Montmartre neighborhood,one of the citys most charming
        neighborhoods. Sample delicacies like croissants and éclairs at a local patisserie, enjoy a guided tasting of
        various cheeses at a fromagerie and satisfy your sweet tooth at a classic chocolaterie. Of course no gourmet
        tour of Paris would be complete without a stop at a boulangerie, where you will learn the proper way to eat a
        baguette in France.Montmartre is the perfect district for Paris food tours because of the area\'s flourishing
        restaurant scene, historical culture and charming ambiance. In the past, windmills, farming areas and art
        studios were prominent features of the Montmartre landscape. Now the area boasts an abundance of first-class
        wine bars, fine dining restaurants and rare shops, all adding to its appeal as one of the best and most unique
        food destinations in the world</string>
    <string name="zurichcruise">Discover the picturesque beauty of Lucerne on a full-day trip from Zurich.
        Cruise the shimmering surface of Lake Lucerne during a tranquil boat ride; absorb gorgeous panoramas of the
        Albis Pass mountain range and explore the historically rich city independently during some leisurely free time.
        Delve into Lucerne\’s fascinating past on a guided sightseeing tour and listen to illuminating commentary
        from an expert guide.Enjoy the convenience of round-trip transportation from Zurich on this magical excursion.</string>
    <string name="pragueriver">Tap into Prague\'s famous party spirit on this 4-hour evening riverside hangout
        and guided walking tour. Meet up near the Charles Bridge, and enjoy unlimited beer and sangria as you take
        relaxed guided walks around different monuments and the cobbled Mala Strana district. Midway through,
        savor dinner under the bridge, and finish by creating your own street art on the John Lennon Wall.</string>
    <string name="placeholder_cost">50</string>
    <string name="book_now">Book Now</string>
    <string name="overview">Overview</string>
</resources>
